So all in ready is to start the second
match of the tournament.
Pink Panthers versus WTW.
So the men in purple across the field of
the Fatima grounds are fantastic
we call as lords of Mumbai
and pink panthers the men in pink
Vishram Sakre and Rahul Savan the the
opening pair and Ganesh Kadam will start
the proceedings. Here
we go in the f in the count of 5 4 3 2 1
game on
looking to play
some innovation. Very first ball
but
Multiple shot
from
is
gain
And the two runs added into the total.
Pink Panther
That will go all the way for four runs.
That's great.
check. Mike check.
Oh, excellent effort by the fielder
is almost a took a roll of MSD behind
the storm MS Dhoni.
So one was gone 10 for no loss. Pink
Panthers.
for a second over. Tushar Pawar comes
into the attack.
Second match of the tournament in
progress
as the first match was played between
Edmund Titans versus
Aquire Ragnar Titans. Edmmit Titans they
got a victory.
Oh, that's a very good bowling.
And suddenly Messi enters into the
field. Football skills are stopped that
and single taken quickly.
11 for no loss.
Toss up delivery and looking to play for
big one. not
has not got the proper elevation to play
that shot. Ball went towards long for
single runulant
now on strike.
Visham got one boundary eight of five
and let's see.
And that's a good strike that will go.
There's a no fielder the ball.
Oh, that's a very good stop.
We thought the ball will run away for
the boundary, but no. The fielder, it
almost reminds me the fielding side of
Mohammad Ke, Jonty Rods
and the latest trending Glenn Phillips,
one of the fantastic uh legendary
fielders we have seen in the cricketing
era.
Three runs taken, one run save for the
team. Good fielding
15 for no loss.
Very short of pitch length and very much
outside the leg line for wide. Umpire
Mr. Noshad Khan signaling that wide
solar run co
that's a full line up and over
just a single
at midoff.
So good start from Rahul and Vishram
and let's see if they can continue the
momentum as a playing run of 10.20 two-0
very good bowling
into the block hole to Sharp Pawar. Very
good bowling. One run conceded only now.
Eight runs conceded so far and last ball
coming up of the second over. 18 for no
loss.
And that's beaten completely. End of the
over. Two gone. 18 for no loss.
Panthers.
So two gone 18 for no loss
or
onfield pitch.
Who will bowl the next over?
That's the end of the power play.
That's end of the power play. Maximum
filters can be outside the circle but
the four fielders minimum should be
inside the circle.
again the
we'll wait for umpire signal
that came not from the bat batsman
misses keeper misses and two runs two
buys
20 for no loss
once again looking to connect completely
missed it good bowling from Venod
and Rahul is just looking to play
towards that square leg region, his
strongest area.
And that's good strike. The fielder is
running. The ball is going, but the ball
will win the race. Four rounds.
Good strike from Raul. That's what he
was looking for and finally has got the
boundary with that. Four runs 24 on the
board. Pink Panthers.
Now there's a fielder standing a deep
backward square leg.
So two fielders
backward square leg and square leg. Deep
square leg. There's a fielder at mid
wicket also. Now
a bit of mid wicket and corn cow corner.
Looking for the reverse with the big
uphill. Big shout
but not out.
So only four runs given by Vinod.
Excellent
bowling once again not able to connect
Rahul Sant.
Oh, that's a good strike. Very good
stop.
And that's end of the over. Three gone.
25 for no loss. Pink Panthers.
So, seven runs came in the previous
over.
Rahul Sant
a beautiful sneakers shining white
I will request one more copy from him
oh that's very good bowling
but Rahul will say this a limited
edition what I'm wearing
but runner
pink panthers
Short pitch ball
only a single bit of due factor still on
not getting the properly
timed really well the batter but they're
not getting the proper elevation to play
big hits. Mahesh Bosley into the attack.
Tap and play. Just guiding the ball
toward that third man region. The ball
will stop before crossing the boundary
line. They're looking for three, but oh,
there's something mix up. Direct hit
could be the chance. The throw was not
that fine
from the non striker to the non- striker
end.
29 for no loss.
And that's played up and over. One
bounce into the fence.
Four runs. Wow. So beautiful. So
elegant. Just looking like a Wow.
33 for no loss. Two boundaries from
Vishram and one from Rahul.
3.333
very much outside the off line.
wide plus one run two run extra added
pink panther will set up the big score
let's see 50 plus will be the
challenging total to WDW
going back for good strike but only a
single at square
36 for no loss.
Oh, that's a very good bowling.
Completely missed it. looking to connect
but beaten. 36 for no loss. Last ball
coming up of the fourth over.
11 of the over so far
once again. Very good bowling. If you
are a medium pacer, this is the pitch
for you. Four was gone. 36 for no loss.
Pink Panthers coming up the last of the
first innings.
Venode into the attack for the last over
the first inning. Try to bowl. Oh,
trying to bowl that leg cutter
but going down the leg side for wide.
As we say for the left arm spin, left
arm orthodox
will get only single. We're talking
about that 50 plus. Let's see. Visam and
Rahul they have the ability to play the
big hittings. 38.
Akri P gain this P party.
Excellent timing for four.
Ball be four because
more biram.
Visam with that three fours 19 of 12.
Rahul 14 of 14 with 14
once again looking to play cut short.
But what was that? It was a chance. A
big smile on the on his face. Wicket
keeper.
43 for no loss. Went for one by.
That's a good strike. High in the air.
They'll go for two easily
and they get two runs.
45 for no loss. Last two balls coming
up.
Will they get 50 plus or will they reach
till 50
down the track
runner up
46 last ball coming up of the first
inning. Here we go. Winner to Vishram.
Fultos ball missed it completely and
that's dot ball to end. So five was
gone. 46 for no loss. Pink Panthers
and 47 to win will be challenging to
chase. Stay tuned for the live action.
WTW need 47 to win.
Hello and welcome back once again to the
ICA Lombard presents Brokers Premier
League 2026
season 3 Mumbai edition
and the Pink Panthers on the field.
A fantastic shining jersey of Pink
Panthers.
requesting a team WDW batter
as Mr. Himmanu sir is ready sir batting
waiting for the one team also to play in
this tournament all are
excited once again
the one one team orange army last orange
So I will request [laughter]
after winning the match.
Here we are the two batters
from the dugout. A big whistle. Podu
whistling.
>> 47 to chase. Not easy.
And the Pink Panthers completing their
huddle.
So welcome back once again to the second
innings of play of the second match of
the tournament. WTW need 47 runs all in
readiness. Ganesh Kadam
will take strike and Vishwak and
Mashilkar
non- strike with a new green ball.
and Pratik Kadam will start. So,
Sec
totally
Mr. PK to Mr. GK.
There's a one fielder at deep extra
cover.
The two fielders outside the circle, one
at Longone.
Wow. Excellent.
That's a good strike for four runs.
Waited for the ball. slicing it nicely
beats the fieldder and a cracking
boundary from Ganesh Kadam.
Fielder deep extra cover deep backward
deep point.
It's a quick change in the field
settings.
Mr. PK to GK.
Oh, THAT'S A GOOD STRIKE. THAT'S gone
high in the air. One bounce into the
fence. Wish long off for a boundary.
The ball was just about to enter the
washroom.
He runs. Wow. Ganesh Kadam backto- back
four.
Good batting.
Damar Shandar Damaar
capitalizing the power play.
played a really fine up and over long
off for four. Again, there's a field
setting change deep points fielder deep
extra cover.
Let's see now what Ganesh Gadam
where he will focus
to score many runs. Oh that's a very
good bowling from
PK
Pratik Kalam. Only a single run this
time. Good. Come back.
Oh,
and that's a good shot once again.
But the ball will stop before crossing
the boundary line.
And very good start from team D WDW. One
was gone, 12 for no loss. They need 35
runs and 24 balls.
One was gone. 12 for none. Rahul seventh
70 number jersey.
70 number jersey SN kra for a reason.
need to come back the team pink
panthers.
They were looking for the wicket.
That's a very good run up. Good strike.
There's a fielder standing
at
mid wicket. Very good throw. That was
excellent throw
but two runs taken.
run up score of WTW
going back and playing it. A good stop
by the fielder at Midon.
>> Oh, great effort. Great effort. Wow,
good fielding.
Excellent work. Only a single run given
15 for no loss.
Ganesh Kadam
back on strike. 11 of five with two
fours.
That's a good strike in the air and
taken by Pratik.
>> The 80 number jersey on his back
and second Pratik coming
to that appreciation.
Second wicket fall of WTW.
First wicket fall indeed.
So 1.315 for one.
The new batter
leftander on strike.
Tucks it away for a single run. Easy
single do of the mark.
We have Vishwa Kiran and Veno the double
V on the crease.
31 run needed from coming 20 balls.
Oh, that's a good strike up and over.
Excellent timing.
That will go all the way for four runs.
And look at the signal from the umpire.
Capitalize the power play
over the midonfielder for four runs.
First boundary from Vishwakan's bat and
last ball coming up of the second over.
24-1
WTW.
Looking London talking Tokyo high in the
air and oh
though no fielder
morning nap but there he has got some
hurt
and both the fielders was attempting to
take that catch but one fielder well
taken there.
Anil has taken that catch.
Ball puna or wicket
ball.
Rahul S 108 for two
bowling by Kadam.
New batsman VBO will face the first ball
as a two-fielder. One at mid wicket, one
at cow corner,
one at deep point
and one at long off. Long gone.
It's completely beaten there. Good
bowling.
It's looking to play offside.
Missed it completely.
26 needed from 2.4 overs to win this
match.
Pink Panthers will look for wicket.
He's got that outside edge. The fielder
at third man for a single run.
That's a lefty righty combination
burning the calories of the opposition.
We had a fantastic lefty righty
combination from Australia's side. Ricky
Ping and Matthew Hayden, one of the
legendary batters
from Australia.
2003 World Cup. Still remember
Excellent
balling into the block hole
just a single.
So talking about the era of 2003 World
Cup witnessed a fantastic match but
India lost in the final with Australia
and they still remember one March 2003
India versus Pakistan
and Sachin got out of 98.
A different era for Indian cricket team.
Meanwhile coming back to the match. Oh
that's out gone.
Caught behind the third wicket fall and
Pratik Kadam has got the breakthrough
here.
So three was gone. 23 for three or
important over crucial over the match
coming up.
One bowler can bowl two overs.
So total four bowlers.
Three was going 23 for three. 24 runs
and 12 balls. Here we go.
No runs there. Good bowling.
This is only over Haymon,
can defend for the team. He will try his
level best to bowl.
Two, three runs, five runs will be the
only
ask from Hmon in this over
the captain of Pink Panthers. Hmon.
Going down the leg side for wide
>> and just over the fielder but there's a
back of fielder was there. Chance for
the run out and gone. Good throw.
It's very important.
There was a backup fielder. A quick
reflexes.
Mahes the new batter first ball. Ohatch
previous ball they got run out and this
could be the one more wicket.
Interesting match.
That's a very good bowling.
20 runs in eight balls.
Utam again.
Excellent attempt by the fielder by
Pratik.
A bit of misjudgment there. Couldn't get
hold of it. And two runs taken.
Pink Panthers. Yeah. WTW
need that one big hit at least in this
coming ball.
18 runs, seven balls.
Well left by the batter going outside
the off jump line for wide.
17 to get from seven balls.
Just a single they will get. Very good
bowling from Haymon. Eight run conceded
only.
Four was gone. 31 for four or Solar
16 runs in six balls.
And after this match coming up, match
number three that will be against
Aquirus Ragnar Titans versus the match
two loser.
Team Aquarius Ragnal Titan. Match number
three.
circular.
Got him.
Vikas
gained catches wins matches.
Ping Panthers
Rahul Nak catch
4.13145 All right.
Very important match for both the teams.
Tushar Paw the new batter coming at
number seven P gain or Solaran. Here we
go.
And very easy catch got behind.
One more wicket fall.
Simple catch.
31 for six. Back to back wicket. And
Vikar's
now on a hat-tick
caught behind Visham.
Char solar run and Vikas Shukla on hat
trick.
Sohan on strike charis
gained hattick a chance gained safe oh
that's a due factor
sloppy on the field
need to take care of it because maybe
you But hurt of that due factor on the
field. Still on
two bigots and one boundary or two fours
and one six.
Yes, that's a very good bowling. Now
coming to fair deliveries.
Team WW.
Slow ball. Excellent bowling. Say clever
bowling from Vikas Shukla.
Just one ball left and 14 runs to get.
Catch
Shand
or saw this match. It's called